A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Activities, Series A FA338
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Middle East Trip, 1977
  - Syria, 1977 (Box 161, Folder 1789)
    Arrangements, thank you cables and letters from NAR to various Syrian officials and hosts, a schedule of appointments and letters introducing Canzeri, Whyte, Kehoe and Murphy who made a follow up visit. NAR correspondence with Richard W. Murphy and President al-Asad regarding the establishment of Sarabam, including a letter in Arabic from NAR to Prince Fahd and other members of the Saudi Royal Family with several drafts and a translation. Letter from Syrian Deputy Minister of Foreign Affairs Abdullah al-Khani thanking NAR for a Steuben glass figure NAR sent as a gift.
  - Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 161, Folder 1790)
    A list of those traveling with NAR and those in the advance team, thank you letters to French and British hosts and officials, two NAR letters to Alfred L. Atherton, U.S. Assistant Secretary of State for Near East and South Asian Affairs, regarding the trip, one letter from Atherton to NAR, a list of gifts presented to heads of state and other officials (gilt bowls, dishes, platters, candelabra, and copies of "Asmat"). Also included are a memo from NAR to Laurance Spelman Rockefeller and David Rockefeller regarding the Saudi Royal Family's desire to set up a family foundation, a resume for Dr. John S. Foster, and a newspaper clipping on a Sudanese investment project.
  - NAR Notes, 1977 (Box 161, Folder 1791)
    Seventy-eight pages of notes in NAR's hand recording his thoughts on the purpose of Sarabam and his observations after his visits. There are typed drafts of some notes. Some of the notes appear to have been made in preparation for his meeting in Saudi Arabia with Prince Fahd and Prince Abdullah of the Saudi royal family. The notes cover the points NAR wanted to make in his effort to "sell" the Saudis on Sarabam including his assessment of the Mid-East situation, and how a joint investment project would foster economic development and thereby promote peace, stability and prosperity and thwart the spread of communism in the region. These points were condensed and typed on a set of fourteen 5x8 inch file cards with the following titles: Peace in the Middle East; Economic Perspective; Two Families Joining Together (Rockefeller and Saud); Food and Energy; Advantages to a Joint Venture; Philosophy; Contributions of Each Side; Outline; Description of Management; and Boycott. There are also twelve pages of stenographer's notes taken at a thirty five minute meeting between NAR, Crown Prince Fahd and Prince Abdullah. The Crown Prince made no commitments.
- Sarabam Corporation, 1977
  - Statements of Purpose, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 1792)
    Several drafts of "Sarabam Statement," citing the corporation's objectives and purpose, Sarabam's proposed structure, and "Summary of the Sarabam Venture" in Arabic and English, covering its objectives, purposes, philosophy and structure. Also included are two memos to NAR regrading a "Daily News" article on Sarabam.
  - By-Laws and Certificate of Incorporation, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 1793)
    Certificate of Incorporation, unsigned, prepared by Debevoise, Plimpton, Lyons and Gates. Draft copy of by-laws, dated March, 1977.
  - Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 1794)
    Included are the Sarabam N.V. Shareholders Agreement, the Sarabam N.V. Class B Voting Agreement, a time schedule of actions to be taken by Sarabam N.V. and the Sarabam Corporation, two drafts of the articles of incorporation of Sarabam N.V., an outline of the legal structure of Sarabam N.V. and the Sarabam Corporation, two drafts of an outline of the corporate structure of Sarabam N.V. and the Sarabam Corporation and the Sarabam N.V. Consent of Shareholder in Lieu of Annual Meeting document with a balance sheet and a statement of operations. Sarabam was divided into two separate entities, Sarabam N.V., "the funding company," based in Curacao in the Dutch Antilles, and Sarabam Corporation, "the operating company," based in New York City.
  - Legal Agreements, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 1795)
    Included are three drafts of the Sarabam Nominee Agreement, three drafts of the Sarabam Option Agreement, three drafts of the Sarabam Corporation Class B Ownership Agreement and two drafts of the Sarabam Corporation Class B Voting Agreement, two drafts of a loan agreement between Sarabam and "RCI" (Rockefeller Center, Inc.?), one draft of the Sarabam Corporation Shareholders' Agreement, page ten of the Revised Outline of Sarabam's Basic Structure, two drafts of Sarabam's Operating Agreement, drafts of the Sarabam Employment Agreement with Arthur Taylor, a letter to NAR explaining the employment agreement, another copy of the Certificate of Incorporation, and resolutions adopted by the Sarabam Board of Directors accepting offers by NAR, chairman, and William J. Ronan, secretary and treasurer, to waive their salaries.
  - Legal Agreements, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 1796)
  - Memoranda on Legal Structure, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 1797)
    Memo from Arthur R. Taylor to NAR and draft of letter from Taylor to Minister Abalkhail, Saudi Arabian Minister of Finance, both regarding legal structure. Draft outlines of Sarabam's legal structure and corporate structure.
  - Budget Memoranda, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 1798)
    Included are a copy of a Sarabam Corporation check for $33,870 made out to NAR, financial statements for the Sarabam Corporation and Sarabam N.V. for the fiscal year ending 6/30/77, and a memo from William J. Ronan to NAR regarding Sarabam expenses and the need for an additional advance.
  - Memoranda on Venture Investments, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 1799)
    Memo from Dick Parsons to NAR with two copies of a series of papers on possible areas of major venture investments. These areas include advanced recovery techniques for oil and gas, solar energy, energy conservation, synthetic fuel production, desalination, hydroponics and microbial food production.
  - Minutes, Board of Directors Meetings, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 1800)
    Included in this folder are the minutes of the 4/14/77, 9/12/77 and 12/9/77 meetings of the Sarabam Board of Directors, the proposed agenda for the 4/14/77 meeting, letter from Oscar M. Ruebhausen to William J. Ronan regarding minutes and sale of stock, and a memo from Kathy Huldrum to NAR reminding him of the May 24, 1977 IBM Board and Executive Committee Meeting.
  - Stock Distribution, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 1801)
  - Stock Options and Dividends, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 1802)
    Included is a proposed guideline for the payment of dividends, a cable from NAR to J. Richardson Dilworth revising "the Center's" (Rockefeller Center?) option to buy Sarabam stock, copies of checks from the Sarabam Corp. to NAR being interest payment on his loan to Sarabam and his salary as Chairman (which he later waived), letter to the Guardian Chemical Corporation from Evelyn Sommer regarding a US patent for a process to recover tars.
  - Trusts, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 1803)
    Management, employees.
  - Staff Biographies, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 1804)
    Resumes for George David Woods, J. Richardson Dilworth, William J. Ronan, Arthur R. Taylor and David O. Beim.
  - OPEC Study, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 1805)
    "OPEC Surpluses and the Disequilibrium in International Payments," 16 pages, with cover letter from Milton Gilbert, Switzerland, to J. Richardson Dilworth.
- Subseries 2, 1941-1980; 2; 15 document box(es)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Subseries 2 is open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Material in the Rockefeller family collections that provides the names, correspondence, or activities of living members of the Rockefeller family, and/or documents the net wealth of any Rockefeller family members, is restricted.
  Scope and Contents Note
  This subseries contains papers on Nelson A. Rockefeller's personal investment and social activities from the early 1940s through the 1970s. It also includes responses to condolences received by his wife, Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller, that were sent in 1979 and 1980. Prior to 2019, it was closed to research due to privacy restrictions.
  Much of the correspondence is routine. However, the files on the Rockefeller Brothers Fund from the 1970s document the efforts to redefine the mission of that philanthropic organization, while the real estate files on the Pocantico, New York, family estate address the planning in advance of its designation as a historic property.
  Of particular note are the files from the two years between Mr. Rockefeller's vice presidential tenure and his death in 1979. This constitutes copies of outgoing correspondence but includes documentation of personal projects he initiated after a lengthy career in public service. Among them was a newly launched book-publishing venture on his art and automobile collections. Also, correspondence with Douglas Dillon in 1978 describes the transfer of the collections of Mr. Rockefeller's Museum of Primitive Art in New York to the Metropolitan Museum of Art.
  - American-Colombian CorporationGeneral, 1941-1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American-Colombian CorporationJesse H. Knight, 1941-1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American-Colombian CorporationStock Holdings and Transactions, 1941-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American-Colombian CorporationStock Agreement, June 27, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bell and Howell, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Christmas Thank-Yous (Incoming from Family), 1960-1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Christmas Thank-Yous (Incoming from Family) (Box 1, Folder 6a)
  - Christmas Thank-Yous (Outgoing to Family), 1960-1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Christmas Thank-Yous (Outgoing to Family) (Box 1, Folder 7a)
  - CLOSED FOLDER (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Contributions by Family to AIA and IBEC, 1947-1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Contributions, PoliticalMemoranda, 1954 Elections (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Gifts to Family, 1954-1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 1, Folder 11a)
  - Government Affairs Foundation, 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - InvestmentsUrban National Corporation, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Loans to Individuals, 1953-1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.General Correspondence, 1947-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Rockefeller Brothers Meetings, 1948-1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Handling Classified Materials, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Finances, NAR Participation, 1946-1951 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Incorporation, Correspondence, 1946, 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Bertol Aircraft Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Compagnie Generale d'Automobiles et d'Aviation au Congo, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Electronic Reduction Corporation, Incorporation, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Electronic Reduction Corporation, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Horizons Inc., 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Island Packers Inc., 1948-1952 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Laboratory for Electronics, 1947-1961 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Marquardt Aircraft, 1950-1952 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.McDonnell-Douglas Corporation, 1948-1949, 1967; 1967 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Minutes of Meetings, 1946-1966 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Nuclear Development Corporation of America, 1956-1961 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Reports, Manual, 1947-1948, 1951-1952, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Societe Generale de Belgique, 1947-1952 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Societe Generale de Belgique, 1950-1960 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Studies, 1949, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.Usines Cotonnieres Africaines (USICAF), 1960, 1963, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc.E. W. Wiggins Airways Inc., 1948-1953 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - CLOSED FOLDER (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Conditions Governing Access Note
  - CLOSED FOLDER (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - CLOSED FOLDER (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - CLOSED FOLDER (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - CLOSED FOLDER (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Toys, 1966-1971 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - CLOSED FOLDER (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - CLOSED FOLDER (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - CLOSED FOLDER (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - TripsEurope, MFR Thank-you Notes, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Wayfarer Ketch CorporationCharter, 1958, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Wayfarer Ketch CorporationCorrespondence, 1956-1971 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Wayfarer Ketch CorporationSail Recommendations, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Wayfarer Ketch CorporationWayfarer Personnel Lists, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - CLOSED FOLDER (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Christmas Gift Files, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 5, Folder 52a)
  - Christmas Gift Files, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 5, Folder 53a)
  - CLOSED FOLDER (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Christmas Gift Files, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - CLOSED FOLDER (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, A, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Ba-Blu, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 5, Folder 58a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Bo-By, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, C, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 5, Folder 60a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, D, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, E-F, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 5, Folder 62a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, G, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, H, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, I-J, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, K, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, L, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 6, Folder 67a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, M, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 6, Folder 68a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, N, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, O, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, P-Q, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 6, Folder 71a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Ra-Ri, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Ro-Ry, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 6, Folder 73a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Sa-Se, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Sh-Sy, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 6, Folder 75a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, T, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, U-W, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, X-Z, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, A, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 7, Folder 79a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Ba-Be, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Bh-By, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Ca, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Ce-Co, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 7, Folder 83a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Cr-Cu, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Da-Di, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Department of Primitive Art, Metropolitan Museum of Art, Primitive Art Inventory, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Do-Du, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 7, Folder 87a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, E, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, F, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 7, Folder 89a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, G, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 7, Folder 90a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, H, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 8, Folder 91a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, I-J, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 8, Folder 92a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, K, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 8, Folder 93a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, L, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Ma-Me, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Mi-Mu, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 8, Folder 96a)
    Conditions Governing Access Notes
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, N, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, O, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 8, Folder 98a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, P-Q, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 8, Folder 99a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Ra-Ry, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 8, Folder 100a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Rockefeller, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - CLOSED MATERIAL (Box 8, Folder 101a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Sa-Sh, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Si-Sy, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 9, Folder 103a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, T-V, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, W, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Y-Z, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, A-D, 1979 January (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, E-H, 1979 January (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, I-O, 1979 January (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 9, Folder 109a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, P-R, 1979 January (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - CLOSED ITEMS, 1979 January (Box 9, Folder 110a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, S-Z, 1979 January (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, NAR's Death, A-M, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 9, Folder 112a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, NAR's Death, N-Z, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Dwayne Andreas (ADM), 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Bob Armeo, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Box 115)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Theodore Braun, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, John S. Foster (TRW), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Susan Herter, Washington, DC, Transition Office, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - CLOSED FOLDER (Box 10, Folder 119)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, William J. Porter, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 120)
  - CLOSED FOLDER (Box 10, Folder 121)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Oscar M. Ruebhausen, Sarabam Corporation, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 122)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 10, Folder 122a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Security Arrangements, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 123)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 10, Folder 123a)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Arthur R. Taylor, Sarabam, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 124)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Edward Teller, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 125)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, George Woods, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 126)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, Yacht Club and Country Club Memberships, 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 127)
  - Post-Vice Presidential Correspondence, NAR Notes on Art Reproduction and Book Publishing Ventures, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 128)
  - Real Estate, 812 Fifth Avenue, Inventory and Appraisal, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 129)
  - Real Estate, Pocantico, Joseph Canzeri, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 130)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 10, Folder 130a)
    Conditons Governing Access Note
  - Real Estate, Pocantico, Joseph Canzeri, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 131)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 10, Folder 131a)
  - CLOSED FOLDER (Box 10, Folder 132)
  - Real Estate, Pocantico, Kykuit Brochure, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 133)
  - Real Estate, Pocantico, Kykuit Vault, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 134)
  - Real Estate, Pocantico, Proposed Lease, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 135)
  - Real Estate, Pocantico, Memoranda, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 136)
  - Real Estate, Pocantico, National Park Service Study of John D. Rockefeller Sr. Estate, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 137)
  - Real Estate, Pocantico, Survey of Historic Houses and Estates, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 138)
  - Real Estate, Pocantico, Rockwood Hall property, c. 1977 (Box 11, Folder 139)
  - CLOSED FOLDER (Box 11, Folder 140)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Memos, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 141)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, David Rockefeller Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 142)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Laurance S. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 143)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 144)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Summary of Activities, Part 1, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 145)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 11, Folder 145a)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Summary of Activities, Part 2, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 146)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 11, Folder 146a)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Correspondence with Family, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - CLOSED ITEMS (Box 11, Folder 147a)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Board of Trustees Objectives, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 148)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Board of Trustees Special Meeting, 1977 September 19 (Box 12, Folder 149)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Executive Committee Agenda, 1977 July 21 (Box 12, Folder 150)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Executive Committee Agenda, 1977 September 22 (Box 12, Folder 151)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Executive Committee Agenda, 1978 February 22 (Box 12, Folder 152)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Funding Proposal Memos, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 153)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Funding Proposal, New York College of Osteopathic Medicine, Grant Proposal, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 154)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Funding Proposal, New York College of Osteopathic Medicine, Background Material, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 155)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Memos, 1977 February-April (Box 12, Folder 156)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Memos, 1977 May-August (Box 12, Folder 157)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Memos, 1977 September-December (Box 13, Folder 158)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Memos, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 159)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Memo Drafts, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 160)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Proposed Operating Procedures, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 161)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Trustee John Gardner, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 162)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Planning Committee Memos to Board, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 163)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Planning Committee NAR Memos, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 164)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Planning Committee Memos to NAR, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 165)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Planning Committee Minutes, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 166)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Planning Committee Report, 1977 November (Box 13, Folder 167)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Planning Committee Report Draft, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 168)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Planning Committee Report Adoption, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 169)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Review Committee, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 170)
  - Laurance Rockefeller Responses to Condolences on NAR's Death, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 171)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Condolences on NAR's Death, 1979 January (Box 14, Folder 172)